<article data-sblg-article="1" data-sblg-tags="about">
	<header>
		<div>
			<h2><a href="#recipe">About Christina</a></h2> 
		</div>
		<nav>
			<a href="#image1"><img src="article009a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		</nav>
		<address>Christina Hallalulu</address>
		<time datetime="2014-08-10">2014-08-10</time>
		<aside>
			Meet Christina Hallalulu, author and founder of the
			recipe blog, Lila,Chop! Clandestine Health food and Living...
			<q>fatally delicious, baking clean with protein powder</q>
			and her Siberian Husky Lila. 
		</aside>
	</header>
	<a id="image1" href="#recipe"><img src="article009a.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image2" href="#recipe"><img src="article009b.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image3" href="#recipe"><img src="article009c.jpg" /></a>
	<section id="recipe">
		<p>
			My name is Christina. I am the owner of the recipe site
			and the instagram account <a
				href="http://instagram.com/project_fitspiration">project_fitspiration</a>.
			Delila-Sky (aka Lila) is my Siberian Husky and muse
			behind the name, Lila, Chop!  
			I am half-Thai, half-Swedish, and passionate
			about everything related to fitness, health,
			gourmet food, travel and Siberian huskies.
			I am also a pilot, and I love to fly. 
		</p> 
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotocspilot.jpg" alt="Christina the pilot" /> 
			<figcaption>Getting my Private Pilot's license</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p> 
			But let's talk about my love of healthy gourmet food&#8211;a supposed
			oxymoron.
		</p>
		<p> 
			Having graduated last year from the world's top hotel
			school, Ecole hôteliere de Lausanne in Switzerland, I
			suddenly found myself with a lot of time on my hands
			and the usual pressing decisions to make about what to
			do with life, career, identiy, et cetera.  
			I certainly didn't feel ready to open up my own hotel
			or start my own chain of restaurants, nor did I feel
			inclined to work split shifts as a chef.  
			But there had to be something I could do with my
			background and food! 
			Something non-traditional, something that would reflect
			my personal journey and beliefs.  
		</p> 
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotovegetarian.jpg" alt="Joke about vegetarians" />
			<figcaption>Vegetarians...</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>	
			Raised as a pesce-vegetarian, and having spent the
			better part of my teens and early twenties
			yo-yo-dieting and obsessively experimenting with
			different food regimes, (vegan, vegetarian,
			gluten-free, raw food, macrobiotic and detox fasts) I
			was fundamentally fed up of dieting and restricting
			myself. 
			I started eating chicken, and for the first
			time in my life this year, tried beef.  
			<i>I actually really liked it!</i> 
		</p>
		<p>
			I have always been a real foodie; some of my
			favourite childhood memories include sampling rare snow
			fish at one of Bangkok's top Italian restaurants, and
			baking Swedish cinnamon buns (<q>kanelbullar</q>) with
			my grandmother.
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotocskdkanebulle.jpg" alt="Me and K, fighting over a kanelbulle" />
			<figcaption>Fighting for the first kanebulle bite with K, who later helped me build Lila, Chop!</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			I love gastronomy, fine-dining and gourmet-cooking with
			luxury ingredients at home such as black truffle and
			lobster.  I love beautifully-presented dishes and that
			moment when the cheese or dessert trolley comes out at
			the end of a meal, right after the bread-crumbing. 
			In fact, I'm a real food snob.  
			But what i can be accused of the most, is that I
			possess a <i>terrible</i> sweet tooth. 

			My favourite desserts in the world include
			molten chocolate (<q>molleaux au chocolat</q>) and sticky
			toffee pudding (how much unhealthier can one's tastes
			get?). 
			Day trip to a chocolate factory for a history of
			chocolate followed by coffee and truffle-pairing?  
			Hell, yes. 

		</p>
		<p>
			Spending four-years at the world's most renown hotel
			school in Switzerland did nothing but cultivate and
			refine my taste and interest in this. 

		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotocslilachocolaterie.jpg" alt="Christina and Lila in a Chocolate factory" />
			<figcaption>Indulging our olfactory senses
				at the chocolate factory in Gruyeres,
				Switzerland.</figcaption> 
		</figure>
		<p> 
			But I had a problem&#8211;I could not coincide this
			with my passion for health and fitness, with my female
			pride of wanting to look good in a bikini, and my sound
			belief in taking care of one's body by nourishing it
			with wholesome, lean and natural foods.
		</p>

		<p>
			That was the perpetual conflict: being a real foodie,
			but also a real health junkie. My taste buds wanted one
			thing, my body said another. 

			Above all, after years of illness and general
			ill-treatment of my own body, I was just starting to
			heal physically. 

			For the first time in my life, I was hitting the gym
			regularly, and hard. 

			Six days a week, two hours a day: weights, and
			adding more strength-training to my previously
			cardio-dominant workouts along with the high intensity
			interval training, bodyrocktv.  

			I began to find myself in the best shape of my life, and
			getting continually stronger, fitter, and leaner every
			month. 
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotoCSlegs.jpg" alt="Christina squatting 60kg" />
			<figcaption>Squatting 60 kg</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			This could only have been possible with the
			right approach to food and nutrition, however.
			You know that saying, <q>you can't out-exercise a bad diet?</q> 
			Well, it's true&#8211; I had to make sure the foods I
			was putting into my body would give me sustained energy
			to last throughout my workouts, and enough protein to
			repair my muscle tissue after.	

			Without wanting to restrict myself and stubbornly
			refusing to get sucked back into any diet mentality, I
			had to learn how to eat properly for this intensity of
			workouts and my fitness goals. 

			Sadly, there seemed to be no room for a gourmet foodie
			in this lifestyle. Only boring cottage-cheese salads,
			egg-white omelettes, cardboard-tasting protein bars and
			grainy, protein shakes! 

			(And every time such dire thoughts crossed my mind, I
			would find myself inexplicably fantasising about ice
			cream.)
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotocseatalltheicecream.jpg" alt="Christina posing for magnum ice cream" />	
			<figcaption>Pouting for some magnum, even in Phuket Thailand paradise</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			Fortunately, I found a way around that &#8211;the perfect
			compromise between food, fitness and figure: clean
			cooking and baking. 

			By clean, I mean using natural, whole, organic,
			unprocessed  ingredients. Ingredients low
			in sugar and fat, that are predominantly gluten- and
			lactose-free. And then protein powder, of course. 
			
			Thanks to Instagram, I found hundreds of recipe ideas
			from fellow health-foodies, and tips from
			fitness models on how to make decadent, protein-rich
			desserts worthy of still being called 
			<q>pre- or post-workout meal</q>. 

			By protein-rich, I mean incorporating protein
			powder into the actual recipes themselves. 
			In fact, I learned that the one major secret ingredient
			was baking with <b>protein powder</b>.  
			I call this the sex appeal behind my healthy creations,
			because it's the one ingredient that spiffies up my
			creations in terms of consistency, flavour, sweetness
			and nutritional value.
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotosbackday.jpg" alt="Christina on the lat pull-down machine" />
			<figcaption>Here I am, on the lat pull-down machine, well-nourished and working hard!</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			I began experimenting, and inviting my girlfriends
			over for Sunday brunch to taste my clean, healthy
			and protein-filled creations. 

			Everything from two-layered frozen smoothies to protein
			pancakes to home-made protein bars and cheesecake... it
			was decadent. It was incredible. It was a foodie's heaven. 
			And I realised I was <i>good</i> at it.
			Pretty soon all my friends were asking me for my
			recipes, and I could not keep up with scribbling them
			down on post-its or posting them in the Instagram
			comments of my photos. 
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotobrunchcollage.jpg" alt="Christina's healthy brunch recipes" />	
			<figcaption>Success of the healthy girl's brunch chez-moi</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			One day, someone very special to me called K, decided
			to help me finally start my own blog. 

			Being the most regular sampler of all my recipes, he
			knew more about my protein creations and the process
			behind them than anyone else. 

			Wracking our minds for a suitable name (<q>the protein
				bakery</q> seemed too generic) he was inspired by my
			beloved Lila, the travelling husky and cat-connoisseur.
			The dog who is known for her refined tastes and
			response to the <q><b>Chop!</b></q> command, and who can be
			expected to make a sudden appearance in the kitchen
			when I'm baking, deserves to name my online cafe and
			recipe collection. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Thus, <b>Lila, Chop!</b> was born.  
			The online cafe and recipe blog that promises 
			<i><b>Clandestine Health food and Living.</b></i>
				<q>Fatally delicious, baking clean with protein
					powder.</q> 
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutmephotolilaroomservice.jpg" alt="Lila with doggy room-service" />
			<figcaption>Lila with doggy roomservice</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<div class="fb-like" data-layout="standard" data-action="like" data-show-faces="false" data-share="true"></div>
	</section>
	<nav>
		<a href="#image1"><img src="article009a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
	</nav>
</article>
