<article data-sblg-article="1" data-sblg-tags="about">
	<header>
		<div>
			<h2><a href="#recipe">About Lila, Chop!</a></h2> 
		</div>
		<address>Christina Hallalulu</address>
		<time datetime="2014-08-10">2014-08-10</time>
		<aside>
			About the <span
				class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> recipe blog: how
			to use it, navigation, and the making of the
			website.
		</aside>
	</header>
	<div id="image1" class="navimage">
		<a href="#image3"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-left fa-fw"></i></a>
		<a href="#"><img src="${sblg-base}a.jpg" alt="${sblg-titletext}" /></a>
		<a href="#image2"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-right fa-fw"></i></a>
	</div>
	<div id="image2" class="navimage">
		<a href="#image1"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-left fa-fw"></i></a>
		<a href="#"><img src="${sblg-base}b.jpg"  alt="${sblg-titletext}"/></a>
		<a href="#image3"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-right fa-fw"></i></a>
	</div>
	<div id="image3" class="navimage">
		<a href="#image2"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-left fa-fw"></i></a>
		<a href="#"><img src="${sblg-base}c.jpg"  alt="${sblg-titletext}"/></a>
		<a href="#image1"><i class="fa fa-lg fa-arrow-right fa-fw"></i></a>
	</div>
	<section id="recipe">
		<p> 
			Dear fellow Chopper,
		</p>
		<p>
			As you are reading this site, you are obviously
			interested in healthy food and delicious recipes. 
			You may be a gourmet-foodie, a health-junkie, or a
			fitness-addict.  
			You may be on a restrictive diet due to health reasons, 
			have special dietary requirements due to competitive
			sports, or on an elimination diet due to food
			intolerances and struggling to find recipes that don't
			taste like sandpaper. 
			Or you might simply be a health-conscious
			person interested in ways to increase your
			protein-intake in an easily creative and delicious way. 
		</p>
		<p>	
			Whatever the reason, welcome to <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> 
			My primary goal with this recipe blog is to provide you with
			simple recipes that look sinfully delicious yet are nutritiously healthy. 
		</p>
		<p>
			My secondary goal was to create a recipe website myself. 
			There are a lot of blogging tools out there, ones that
			I have used before and found easy but limiting. I did
			not want to find myself stuck with someone else's
			template, or unable to add cool features (such as the
			change servings tool!) as I wish. 
			So with the help, and support of K, I decided to
			take the time to learn HTML, CVS, CSS, 
			<a href="http://www.vim.org/">vim</a>, and Unix, in order to
			build this website and create all the recipes myself in
			terminal. The site is powered by the
			<a href="http://kristaps.bsd.lv/sblg/">sblg</a> system on
			<a href="http://www.openbsd.org/">OpenBSD</a>.
			I must say, it's far more awesome to do it
			this way. Who says chicks can't learn to
			program?
		</p>
		<p>
			If you choose to post photos of your results from my
			recipes or to re-post the recipes themselves, be sure to
			cite me!  Likewise, I make sure to cite all the recipes
			I adapt and find inspiration from.  
		</p>
		<p>
			Happy baking, and namnam.
		</p>
		<p>
			Christina &amp; Lila
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachopterminal.jpg" alt="Terminal screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Building <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> in Terminal.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		
		<p> 
			<b>Home page</b>
		</p>
		<p> 
			This is the home page, where you can see a blog-roll of
			the latest articles and recipes.  
			On the left-hand navigation pane, you will see a list
			of articles by tags, such as recipes by
			nutritional profile: gluten-fee, low-Carb, vegan,  et
			cetera, or recipes by type: smoothie, cake, savoury
			dishes, et cetera. (On a smart phone, you will not see
			the navigation pan. Use the <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> 
			website title and the 
			<i class="fa fa-archive"></i> archive button to
			navigate instead.)
		</p>			
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachopsmartphone.jpg" alt="Smartphone view" /> 
			<figcaption>iPhone navigation pane.</figcaption>
		</figure>
	
		<p>	
			At the bottom of the page you will see a link to the
			<i class="fa fa-archive"></i> 
			archives, where you will find a list of all my recipes.
			You can always navigate back home by clicking on the 
			<span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> website title.
			Want to like and share this blog on 
			<i class="fa fa-facebook-square"></i>
			Facebook, follow me personally on 	
			<i class="fa fa-instagram"></i>
			Instagram, get recipe updates with
			<i class="fa fa-rss"></i>
			RSS, or 
			<i class="fa fa-envelope"></i>
			email me? 
			Click on the icons at the top of
			the page.
		</p>
		<p>	
			I will always appreciate personal feedback and
			comments about my site, and try to answer questions as
			promptly as I can. 
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachophomepage.jpg" alt="Home page screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Home page.</figcaption>
		</figure>
	
		<p> 
			<b>Recipe page</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			Check out the nutritional information and the
			food-icons to see exactly what kind of nutritional
			profile each recipe has! 
			By hovering your mouse over each icon, you can see what
			the icon indicates: 
			<img class="hicon" src="glutenfree.png" alt="Gluten-free"/> gluten-free,
			<img class="hicon" src="lactosefree.png" alt="Lactose-free"/> lactose-free,
			<img class="hicon" src="sugarfree.png" alt="Sugar-free"/> sugar-free,
			<img class="hicon" src="lowcarb.png" alt="Low-Carb"/> low-carb,
			<img class="hicon" src="lowfat.png" alt="Low-Fat"/> low-fat,
			<img class="hicon" src="highprotein.png" alt="High-Protein"/> high-protein,
			<img class="hicon" src="raw.png" alt="Raw"/> raw,
			<img class="hicon" src="vegan.png" alt="Vegan"/> vegan, and
			<img class="hicon" src="paleo.png" alt="Paleo"/> paleo.
			The macro-nutrient information, or <q>macros</q>as I
			call them, (calories &#x007C; grams protein &#x007C; grams
			carbs &#x007C; grams fat) are stated per serving.
			The number of servings each recipes makes is indicated
			underneath the ingredients list, along with the total
			calories for the entire recipe.  
			Remember, you can always adapt recipe ingredients to
			your liking, and change the serving amounts using the
			change servings tool.  
			
		</p>
		<p>
			The ingredients I use are clean and wholesome. Most of
			my recipes are gluten, lactose and soy-free, and a lot
			of them feature protein powder as a key ingredient.  
			I link the products I use to 
			<img class="hicon" src="amazon.png" alt="Amazon"/> Amazon so you can buy them online yourselves. 
			(Note that  <b>all</b> the products I mention are ones I have
			chosen to use myself, because I find them of
			superior quality and taste, suitable for my recipes and
			of course, nutritious.) 

		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoprecipepage1.jpg" alt="Recipe page ingredients and instructions screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Recipe ingredients and instructions.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p>
			By clicking on one of the recipe thumbnails, you will
			see a full-screen photo of the recipe. Browse through
			the various recipe photos, and feel yourself start to
			salivate!  
			Click on the recipe name to get back to the recipe ingredients
			and instructions page.  
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoprecipepage2.jpg" alt="Recipe page photos screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Recipe photos.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		
		<p> 
			<b>Archive page</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			Click on the
			<i class="fa fa-archive"></i> archive icon at the top of the page to see
			a full list of recipes and articles in chronological
			order.  Be prepared to scroll down, there will be many
			and many more to come!
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoparchivepage.jpg" alt="Archive page screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Archive page with full list of recipes.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<div class="fb-wrapper">
			<div class="fb-like" data-layout="standard" data-action="like" data-show-faces="false" data-share="true"></div>
		</div>
	</section>
</article>
