<article data-sblg-article="1" data-sblg-tags="about">
	<header>
		<div>
			<h2><a href="#recipe">About Lila, Chop!</a></h2> 
		</div>
		<nav>
			<a href="#image1"><img src="article010a.thumb.jpg" alt="Valentines day protein muffins" title="Valentines day protein muffins" /></a>
			<a href="#image2"><img src="article010b.thumb.jpg" alt="Lila begging for some ice cream" title="Lila begging for some ice cream" /></a>
			<a href="#image3"><img src="article010c.thumb.jpg" alt="What it takes to make a protein smoothie" title="What it takes to make a protein smoothie" /></a>
		</nav>
		<address>Christina Hallalulu</address>
		<time datetime="2014-08-10">2014-08-10</time>
		<aside>
			About the <span
				class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> recipe blog: How
			to use it, our promise to you, and the making of the
			website.
		</aside>
	</header>
	<a id="image1" href="#recipe"><img src="article010a.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image2" href="#recipe"><img src="article010b.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image3" href="#recipe"><img src="article010c.jpg" /></a>
	<section id="recipe">
		<p> 
			Dear fellow Chopper,
		</p>
		<p>
			As you are reading this site, you are obviously
			interested in healthy food and delicious recipes. 
			You may be a gourmet-foodie, a health-junkie, or a
			fitness-addict.  
			You may be on a restrictive diet due to health reasons, 
			have special dietary requirements due to competitive
			sports, or on an elimination diet due to food
			intolerances and struggling to find recipes that don't
			taste like sandpaper. 
			Or you might simply be a health-conscious
			person interested in ways to increase your
			protein-intake in an easily creative and delicious way. 
		</p>
		<p>	
			Whatever the reason, welcome to <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> 
			My goal with this recipe blog is to provide you with
			simple recipes that look sinfully delicious yet are nutritiously healthy. 
			
			The ingredients I use are clean and wholesome. Most of
			my recipes are gluten, lactose and soy-free, and a lot
			of them feature protein powder as a key ingredient.  
			I link the products I use to the websites I bought them
			from, so you can buy them online yourselves. 
			(Note that<b>all</b> the products I mention are ones I have
			choosen to use myself, because I find them of
			superior quality and taste, suitable for my recipes and
			of course, nutritious.) 
		</p>
		<p>
			If you choose to post photos of your creations from my
			recipes or to repost the recipes themselves, be sure to
			cite me!  Likewise, I make sure to cite all the recipes
			I adapt and find inspiration from.  
		</p>
		<p>
			Happy baking, and namnam.
		</p>
		<p>
			Christina &amp; Lila
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>How to use</b> <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span>	
		</p>
		<p> 
			<b>Home page</b>
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachophomepage.jpg" alt="Home page screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Home page.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p> 
			<b>Recipe page</b>
		</p>
		<p>
			Check out the nutritional information and the
			food-icons to see exactly what kind of nutritional
			profile each recipe has! And remember, you can always
			adapt them to your liking and change the serving
			amounts using the change servings tool.  

		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoprecipepage1.jpg" alt="Recipe page ingredients and instructions screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Recipe ingredients and instructions.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoprecipepage2.jpg" alt="Recipe page photos screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Recipe photos.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<p> 
			<b>Archive page</b>
		</p>
		<figure>
			<img src="aboutlilachoparchivepage.jpg" alt="Archive page screen shot" /> 
			<figcaption>Archive page with full list of recipes.</figcaption>
		</figure>
		<div class="fb-wrapper">
			<div class="fb-like" data-layout="standard" data-action="like" data-show-faces="false" data-share="true"></div>
		</div>
	</section>
	<nav>
		<a href="#image1"><img src="article010a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image2"><img src="article010b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image3"><img src="article010c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
	</nav>
</article>
