<article data-sblg-article="1" data-sblg-tags="aboutme">
	<header>
		<div>
			<h2><a href="#recipe">About Christina</a></h2> 
		</div>
		<nav>
			<a href="#image1"><img src="article009a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		</nav>
		<address>Christina Hallalulu</address>
		<time datetime="2014-08-03">2014-08-03</time>
		<aside>
			Meet Christina Hallalulu, author and founder of the
			recipe blog, Lila,Chop! Clandestine Health food and Living...
			"fatally delicious, baking clean with protein powder,"
			and her Siberian Husky Lila, the muse behind the name. 
		</aside>
	</header>
	<a id="image1" href="#recipe"><img src="article009a.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image2" href="#recipe"><img src="article009b.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image3" href="#recipe"><img src="article009c.jpg" /></a>
	<section id="recipe">
		<p>
			My name is Christina, and Delila-sky (or Lila) is my
			Siberian Husky&#8211;the muse behind the name, Lila,Chop!  
			I come from Thailand and Sweden, and I am passionate
			about everything related to fitness, health food,
			gourmet food, travel and siberian huskies.
			I am also a pilot, and I love to fly. 
			<img src="cspilot.jpg" alt="Christina the pilot" /> 
		</p> 
		<p> 
			But let's talk abut healthy gourmet food, a supposed
			oxymoron.

			<img src="cslobster.jpg" alt="Christina eating lobster" />
		</p>

		<p> 
			Having graduated from the world's top hotel school, Ecole
			hôteliere de Lausanne in Switzlernad, I suddenly had
			a lot of time on my hands and the usual choices to make
			about what to do with my life and who I want to be,
			etcetera.  

			<img src= "csapkitchen.jpg" alt="Chrisitna in kitchen uniform" />

		</p>
			
		<p>	
			Raised as a pesce-vegetarian, and having spent the
			better part of my teens and early twenties
			yo-yo-dieting and obsessedly experimenting different food regminss
			(vegan, vegetarian, gluten-free, raw food,
			macrobiotic and detox fasts) I was fundamentally fed up
			of dieting and restricting myself. 
			
			<img src= "vegetarian.jpg" alt="Joke about vegetarians" />

		</p>

		<p>
			
			I have always been a real foodie and known for my sweet
			tooth &#8211;some of my favourite childhood memories
			include trying out Argentenean snow fish at one of
			Bangkok's top Italian restaurants and baking Swedish
			cinnamon buns ("kanelbullar") with my grandmoster in
			Gothenburg.

			<img src="kanelbulle.jpg" alt="Kanelbulle" />
			
		</p>

		<p>
			I love gastronomy, fine-dining, luxury ingredients such
			as white truffle and lobster, and gourmet-cooking at
			home. 

			I will admit a secret here: I have a terrible
			sweet tooth. 

			My favourite desserts in the world include
			molten chocolate ("molleaux au chocolat") and sticky
			toffee pudding (how much unhealthier can one's tastes
			get?). 

			I love visiting chocolate atelieres and sampling
			the richest hand-made truffles creations of the day,
			and buying the finest ingredients to bring back home to
			use in my baking.

			<img src="cslilachocolaterie.jpg" alt="Christina and Lila in a Chocolate factory" />
		</p>

		<p>
			Spending four-years at the most renown hotel
			school in the world did nothing but cultivate and
			refine my taste and interest in this. 

			Furthermore, kitchen practicals gave me ample
			opportunity to refine my baking skills, such as making
			Swedish sticky chocolate cake ("kladdkaka"), one of the
			most norotirously sinfully delicious and unhealthy
			desserts out there, in large quantities. 
			
			<img src="cskladdkakafu.jpg" alt="Christina baking Swedish sticky chocolate cake" />	

		</p>

		<p> 
			But I had a problem&#8211;I could not coincide this
			with my passion for health and fitness, with my female
			pride of wanting to look good in a bikini, and my sound
			belief in taking care of one's body by nourishing it
			with wholesome, lean and natural foods.

			<img src="csgradtrip.jpg" alt="Christina in a bikini and eating dessert and fruit." />	

			That was the perpetual conflict: being a real foodie,
			but also a real health junkie. 

			Above all, after years of illness and general
			ill-treatment of my own body, I was just starting to
			heal physically. 

			For the first time in my life, I was hitting the gym
			regularly, and hard. 

			Six days a week, two hours a day - lifting weights, and
			adding more strength-training to my previously
			cardio-dominant workouts along with high intensity
			interval training.  

			I began to find myself in the best shape of my life, and
			getting continually stronger, fitter, and leaner every
			month. 

			<img src="CSlegs.jpg" alt="Christina squatting 60kg" />

		</p>

		<p>

			This could only have been possible with the
			right approach to food and nutrition, however. 

			Without wanting to restrict myself and stubbornly
			refusing to get sucked back into any diet mentality, I
			had to learn how to eat properly for this intensity of
			workouts, lifestyle and fitness goals. 

			Saldy, there seemed to be no room for a gourmet foodie
			in this picture - only boring cottage-cheese salads,
			egg-white omelets, cardboard-tasting protein bars and
			grainy, protein shakes! 

			(And everytime such dire thoughts crossed my mind, I
			would find myself inexplicably fantasising about ice
			cream.)

			<img src="cseatalltheicecream.jpg" alt="Christina eat all the ice cream" />	

		</p>
		<p>
			Fortunately, I found a way around that &#8211;the perfect
			compromise between fine food and fine health -
			clean-cooking and baking. 

			By clean, I mean using natural, whole, organic,
			predominantly-unprocessed ingredients. 
			
			Thanks to instagram, I found hundreds of recipe ideas
			from fellow gourmet health-foodies, and tips from
			fitness models on how to make decadent, protein-rich
			desserts. 

			By protein-rich, I mean incorporating protein
			powder into the actual recipes themselves. 
			In fact, I learned that the one major secret ingredient
			was baking with RPOTEIN POWDER.  
			I call this the sex appeal behind my healthy creations,
			because it's the one ingredient that spiffies up my
			creations in terms of consistency, flavour, sweetness
			and nutritional value.

			<img src="brunchcollage.jpg" alt="Christina's healthy brunch recipes" />	
		</p>
		<p>
			I began experiementing, and inviting my girlfriends
			over for Sunday brunch to taste out my clean, healthy
			and protein-filled creations. 

			Everything from two-layered frozen smoothies to protein
			pancakes to home-made protein bars and cheesecake... it
			was incredibe. 
			I realised I was GOOD at it.
			I loved making it, and they loved trying it.
			Pretty soon all my friends were asking me for my
			recipes, and I could not keep up with scribbling them
			down on post-its or writing them in the instagram
			comments of my photos. 

			<img src="smoothiescollage.jpg" alt="Smoothies collage" />

		</p>

		<p>
			One day, someone very special to me called K, decided
			to help me finally start my own blog. 

			Being the most regular sampler of all my recipes, he
			knew more about my protein creations and the process
			behind them than anyone else. 

			Wracking our minds for a suitable name ("the protein
			bakery" seemed too generic) he was inspired by my
			beloved Lila, the travelling husky and cat-connoisseur.
			The dog who is known for her refined tastes and
			response to the "Chop! command", and who can be
			expected to make a sudden appearance in the kitchen
			when I'm baking, deserves to name my online cafe and
			recipe collection. 

			<img src="lilaroomservice.jpg" alt="Lila with doggy roomservice" />

		</p>

		<p>
			The was the birth of Lila,Chop! Clandestine Health food
			and Living. 
			<i>Fatally delicious, baking clean with
				protein powder.</i> 
		</p>

			<img src="cslilapuppy.jpg" alt="Christina and Lila" />

		<p>
			<b>Lila,Chop!'s promise to you</b>
			As you are reading this recipe blog, you are obviously
			interested in healthy and delicious food. You may be a
			gourmet-foodie, a health-food junkie, on a restrictive
			diet due to food intolerances, or just interested in
			ways to increase your protein-intake in a delicious
			way. My promise to you with Lila,Chop! is that ALL the
			ingredients I use are healthy, clean and wholesome. I
			link the products I use, so you can buy them online
			yourselves. (All the products I mention are ones I
			choose to use because I personally find them of
			high-quality." Most of the recipes I make are gluten-
			and lactose-free, and almost all of them are high in
			protein. Check out the nutritional informaiton and the
			food-icons to see exactly what kind of nutritional
			profile each recipe has! And remember, you can always
			adapt them to your liking.

		</p>	

	</section>
	<nav>
		<a href="#image1"><img src="article009a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
	</nav>
</article>
