<article data-sblg-article="1" data-sblg-tags="about">
	<header>
		<div>
			<h2><a href="#recipe">About Lila, Chop!</a></h2> 
		</div>
		<nav>
			<a href="#image1"><img src="article010a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
			<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		</nav>
		<address>Christina Hallalulu</address>
		<time datetime="2014-08-10">2014-08-10</time>
		<aside>
			Meet Christina Hallalulu, author and founder of the
			recipe blog <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> 
			Clandestine health food and Living...
			fatally delicious, baking clean with protein powder...
		</aside>
	</header>
	<a id="image1" href="#recipe"><img src="article010a.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image2" href="#recipe"><img src="article009b.jpg" /></a>
	<a id="image3" href="#recipe"><img src="aboutmephotocsmusclebeach.jpg" /></a>
	<section id="recipe">
		<p>
			<b>Our promise to you:</b>
		</p>	
		<p> 
			Dear fellow Chopper,

		</p>
		<p>
			As you are reading this site, you are obviously
			interested in healthy food and delicious recipes. 
			You may be a gourmet-foodie, a health-food junkie, or a
			fitness-addict.  You may be on a restrictive diet due
			to food intolerances and struggling to find ways to
			make bread and desserts that don't taste like
			sandpaper, or your average, health-conscious person
			interested in ways to increase your protein-intake in a
			delicious way. 

		</p>
		<p>	
			My promise to you with <span class="nm">Lila, Chop!</span> is that ALL the
			ingredients I use are healthy, clean and wholesome. I
			link the products I use to the websites I bought them
			from, so you can buy them online yourselves. (<b>all</b> the
			products I mention are ones I choose to use because I
			personally find them of high-quality, suitable for my
			recipes and generally yummy.) 
			Most of the recipes I make are gluten- and
			lactose-free, and almost all of them are high in
			protein. 
			Check out the nutritional information and the
			food-icons to see exactly what kind of nutritional
			profile each recipe has! And remember, you can always
			adapt them to your liking.
			If you choose to post photos of your creations from my
			recipes or to repost the recipes themselves, be sure to
			cite me! 
			Likewise, I make sure to cite all the recipes
			I adapt and find inspiration from.  
			Happy baking, and namnam.
		</p>	
		<div class="fb-like" data-layout="standard" data-action="like" data-show-faces="false" data-share="true"></div>
	</section>
	<nav>
		<a href="#image1"><img src="article009a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image2"><img src="article009b.thumb.jpg" /></a>
		<a href="#image3"><img src="article009c.thumb.jpg" /></a>
	</nav>
</article>
