<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
	<head>
		<meta name="viewport" content="initial-scale=1.0, user-scalable=no" />
		<meta charset='utf-8' /> 
		<meta property="fb:admins" content="501890034" />
		<link rel="stylesheet" href="main.css" type="text/css" />
		<link rel="stylesheet" href="archive.css" type="text/css" />
		<link href="https://maxcdn.bootstrapcdn.com/font-awesome/4.2.0/css/font-awesome.min.css" rel="stylesheet" />
		<title>Lila, Chop!</title>
	</head>
	<body>
		<header>
			<a href="index.html" class="banner"><img src="banner.png" alt="Lila, Chop!" /></a>
			<a href="index.html" class="bannerbg"><img src="bannerbig.png" alt="Lila, Chop!" /></a>
		</header>
		<nav id="subhead">
			<span id="about">
				<a href="article009.html"><img src="article009a.jpg" /></a>
				<a href="article010.html"><img src="article010a.jpg" /></a>
			</span>
			<a href="https://www.facebook.com/lilachop"><i class="fa fa-facebook-square"></i></a>
			<a href="http://instagram.com/Project_fitspiration"><i class="fa fa-instagram"></i></a>
			<a href="atom.xml"><i class="fa fa-rss"></i></a>
			<script>
			<!--
			     // Email obfuscator script 2.1 by Tim Williams, University of Arizona
			     // Random encryption key feature by Andrew Moulden, Site Engineering Ltd
			     // This code is freeware provided these four comment lines remain intact
			     // A wizard to generate this code is at http://www.jottings.com/obfuscator/
			     { 
				coded = "ZlPYgxYc5@3Y35ZlSI.ZSa"
				key = "07QHZrRgSqtayYhBCAw8Tdnzfe6P4JUWx5KXl1LpuvjOc2DsoGEmNiMkF93bVI"
				shift=coded.length
				link=""
				for (i=0; i<coded.length; i++) {
					if (key.indexOf(coded.charAt(i))==-1) {
						ltr = coded.charAt(i)
						link += (ltr)
					} else {     
						ltr = (key.indexOf(coded.charAt(i))-shift+key.length) % key.length
						link += (key.charAt(ltr))
					}
				}
				document.write("<a href='mailto:"+link+"'><i class='fa fa-envelope'></i></a>")
			}
			//-->
			</script>
			<a href="archive.html"><i class="fa fa-archive"></i></a>
		</nav>
		<section>
			<nav data-sblg-nav="1" data-sblg-navsz="5" data-sblg-navcontent="1">
				<figure>
					<a href="${sblg-base}.html"><img alt="${sblg-titletext}" src="${sblg-base}a.thumb.jpg" /></a>
					<figcaption><a href="${sblg-base}.html">${sblg-titletext}</a></figcaption>
				</figure>
			</nav>
			<article>
				<section>
		<!--!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!-->
		<h1>
			Disclaimer
		</h1>
		<p>
			This website, as well as all the material on this website (including, without
			limitation, the text, source code, photographs, images,) are property of Christina
			Sophonpanich and are copyright protected under Lila, Chop! 2014. 
		</p>
		<p>
			No part of this website or any of its contents may be reproduced, copied, modified or
			adapted, without the prior written consent of the author, unless otherwise indicated for
			stand-alone materials. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Commercial use and distribution of the contents of the website is not allowed
			without express and prior written consent of the author. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Licensing inquiries and requests for general distribution can be sent out to
			<a href="mailto:christina@lilachop.com">christina@lilachop.com</a>.
		</p>
		<h2>
			SHARING CONTENT
		</h2>
		<p>
			If you would like to share a recipe from this site, you are more than welcome to
			post a photo and link back directly to the recipe and instructions on this site;
			republishing recipes, complete or partial, is strictly forbidden without express and prior
			written consent of the author. Note that making a few minor substitutions or rewriting a
			recipe in your own words does not make said recipe your own. If you liked a recipe enough
			to feel the need to share it, please respectfully link back to the original work. 
		</p>
		<h2>
			AFFILIATE LINKS
		</h2>
		<h3>
			Affiliate Disclosure
		</h3>
		<p>
			Links to products and services on third-party websites (affiliate links) may be
			included in some of my posts. If you click on an affiliate link and make a purchase I may
			receive a small commission, which helps keep this place alive. Certain ads that may appear
			in this site may also contain some of these affiliate links, to which the same
			conditions apply. 
		</p>
		<h2>
			DISCLAIMER
		</h2>
		<h3>
			Accuracy of Information
		</h3>
		<p>
			The information contained in this website is for general information purposes
			only. The information is provided by lilachop.com and whilst we endeavour to keep the
			information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind,
			express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or
			availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or
			related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such
			information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
		</p>
		<p>
			In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation,
			indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from
			loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
		</p>
		<p>
			No representations are made about the accuracy of the information contained in any
			page on this site or referred to from this site, and there is no promise or guarantee that
			anything contained herein is correct, complete or up-to-date.
		</p>
		<p>
			Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under
			the control of lilachop.com. We have no control over the nature, content and
			availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a
			recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.
		</p>
		<h2>
			Privacy Policy
		</h2>
		<p>
			Anonymous visitor information is recorded by Facebook Insights used to determine
			site traffic for the purpose of determining blog growth and site statistics. This
			information is never shared or sold.  Furthermore, this information is gathered through
			the use of cookies, which you have the liberty to turn off at any time by modifying your
			Internet browser’s settings. 
		</p>
		<!--!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!-->
				</section>
			</article>
		</section>
		<footer>
			&#169; 2013, 2014, <q>Lila, Chop!</q>
			<div>
				<a href="disclaimer.html">Terms &amp; Privacy</a>
			</div>
			<div>
				Powered by <a href="http://kristaps.bsd.lv/sblg">sblg</a> on <a href="http://www.openbsd.org">OpenBSD</a>
			</div>
			<div>
				<a href="https://www.facebook.com/lilachop"><i class="fa fa-facebook-square"></i></a>
				<a href="http://instagram.com/Project_fitspiration"><i class="fa fa-instagram"></i></a>
				<a href="atom.xml"><i class="fa fa-rss"></i></a>
				<script>
				<!--
				     // Email obfuscator script 2.1 by Tim Williams, University of Arizona
				     // Random encryption key feature by Andrew Moulden, Site Engineering Ltd
				     // This code is freeware provided these four comment lines remain intact
				     // A wizard to generate this code is at http://www.jottings.com/obfuscator/
				     { 
					coded = "ZlPYgxYc5@3Y35ZlSI.ZSa"
					key = "07QHZrRgSqtayYhBCAw8Tdnzfe6P4JUWx5KXl1LpuvjOc2DsoGEmNiMkF93bVI"
					shift=coded.length
					link=""
					for (i=0; i<coded.length; i++) {
						if (key.indexOf(coded.charAt(i))==-1) {
							ltr = coded.charAt(i)
							link += (ltr)
						} else {     
							ltr = (key.indexOf(coded.charAt(i))-shift+key.length) % key.length
							link += (key.charAt(ltr))
						}
					}
					document.write("<a href='mailto:"+link+"'><i class='fa fa-envelope'></i></a>")
				}
				//-->
				</script>
			</div>
		</footer>
	</body>
</html>
